indiawest.com 2019-05-16

# Privacy Policy | Site | indiawest.com

### Introduction

indiawest.com is the online version of the weekly print newspaper, India-West, that has won more awards than any other Indian American publication in their market. In addition to the articles published in the newspaper, the web portal has a wide range of sections like Life & Style; Blogs/Opinions; Hot Deals; Live Channels; Food; Travel; Matrimonials; Real Estate; Weddings; Events/Tickets; and Photogallery. We are the one-stop-site for the global Indian community’s needs. India-West and indiawest.com cover breaking news, events in the community and a variety of newsworthy information touching the heart of the Indian American community.

### Privacy Policy

indiawest.com wants to make our privacy practices clear and easy to understand. This page provides our current Privacy Policy.

### Scope

indiawest.com Privacy Policy applies to indiawest.com.

### Information We Gather

The information we gather falls into two categories: 1) personal information you voluntarily supply when you subscribe, order, complete a survey, register for an online discussion, enter a contest or provide your e-mail address; and 2) tracking information collected as you navigate through our sites.

### Use of Information

If you have registered online to one of our sites, indiawest.com will not sell, rent, swap or authorize any third party to use your e-mail address without your permission. This also applies to any information that personally identifies you, except as noted immediately below. We do, however, share information about our audience in aggregate form. For example, we may want to know how long the average reader spends on our site or which pages or features get the most attention. indiawest.com may share personal information with our parent company, India-West and India-West Publications, Inc. indiawest.com will not share personal information about you as an individual to third parties without your consent.

indiawest.com may perform statistical analyses of subscribers and their subscribing and purchasing patterns for product development purposes and to generally inform advertisers about the nature of our subscriber base.

We may use demographic and preference information to allow advertising on our Web sites to be targeted, in aggregate, to the users for whom they are most pertinent. We contract with other companies to provide services on our behalf, including but not restricted to credit-card and billing processing, shipping, e-mail distribution, list processing and analytic or promotions management. Any information you disclose when posting to a message board, blog or commenting with your message board screen name or ID, becomes public and may be used by indiawest.com for online and offline promotional or commercial uses in any and all media.

### Your Privacy Choices

If, at any time, you prefer not to receive e-mail marketing information from us, simply follow the unsubscribe options at the bottom of each e-mail. For more information on how to unsubscribe from e-mail marketing, please email us at [web@indiawest.com](mailto:web@indiawest.com) and include the subject line of UNSUBSCRIBE.

### Important Information

We encourage you to read our complete Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to update our Privacy Policy at any time without notice. Our Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time. Any such changes will be posted on our Privacy Policy page. We employ measures designed to protect the security of your personal identifying information.

### How To Contact Us

For any questions or comments regarding our information or security practices, you may contact us by e-mail at [web@indiawest.com](mailto:web@indiawest.com) or by mail at India-West Publications, Inc., 933 MacArthur Blvd, San Leandro, CA 94577 USA.

### About Our Content

Our content is fully copyright protected and cannot be used without permission granted from a senior executive at indiawest.com. To seek permission, just email [web@indiawest.com](mailto:web@indiawest.com)
